https://www.usbgear.com/privacy-policy.html

Firewire Cables
Power over Ethernet (PoE)
usb to serial adapter
USB to Serial Adapters (RS232, RS422 & RS485)
USBGear.com Security and Privacy Statement
At USBGear we protect your credit card information and privacy by using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology (the industry standard security protocol), hosting our site on secure servers, and maintaining Secure Site status.
Secure Credit Card Transactions
When you provide us with any personal information, such as your credit card number when making a purchase, we use SSL data encryption to ensure that no one can read as it is transmitted over the Internet. We use Cookies (small encrypted data files containing references to user ID information that are stored on our secure server and may write to your hard drive) to keep track of your shopping cart. Your information is safely stored behind a firewall that protects it from users from other networks.
Your Personal Information
To process your order, notify you of matters that may be of interest and improve your USBGear.com shopping experience, we collect information, such as e-mail addresses, domain names, the number of visits each page receives, and other information you may volunteer. Any personal information that you submit to the site will remain as safe and secure as your credit card information.
Removal From USBGear.com Lists
You may receive periodic emails or postal mailings from us with information on new products and services, or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive e-mail and/ or postal mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email at [email protected]. USBGear.com does not currently rent, sell or otherwise forward your name or other personal information to other companies.
Links To Other Sites
USBGear.com contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
